Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS 092
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Audio [See also Accretions 2001]
  - Subseries B: Primary Audio Works
    - -Success // Ending loneliness; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony CHF 90, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0238)
    - -Hujar interview, tape 1; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0239)
    - -Phil: Health Stuff // Interview: Mary Hayslip re: Montanna's death 4/9/90 / Phil, Richard last tape; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, 1990 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0240)
    - -Interview with Ruth Hirschman-7/23/90; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0241)
    - -Side 1: Interview with Ruth Hirschman-7/23/90, Side 2: ARTS/LA Tongues of Flame-8/13/90; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0242)
    - -Interview with Susan Wyett/Artists Space, NYC/60 min.; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0243)
    - -Jesse; audiocassette (F-4B) Memorex MRX I 30, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0244)
    - -John/David conversation 12/31/80; audiocassette (F-4B) Scotch Dynarange 90, 1980 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0245)
    - -Journal; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony EF 60, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0246)
    - -Journal #2, 1988-89; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0247)
    - -Junk journal April 27-28, 1982, NYC // Jim Fourat/Junk Tape; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D-C 60 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0248)
    - -KCRW Radio interview with Ruth Hirschman; audiocassette TDK AV-D 120, 1990 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0249)
    - -Loneliness #2; audiocassette (F-4B) Sony CHF 90, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0250)
    - -Hunke/Louis; audiocassette Certron LN 60 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0251)
    - -Some Cats Swing // Louis Cartwright tape 3, Finish up this side / Louis Cartwright 3TK4; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK SD-C 60, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0252)
    - -Louis Cartwright tape 5 / Heavy Truck Drivin Poetry - "And a Happy New Year","Bologna la Influenza (Opera)", "Interrogation"; audiocassette Capitol 60 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0253)
    - -Louis last tape I / II; audiocassette (F-4B) Certron LN 60, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0254)
    - -Louis last tape, Sept. 77 / Another Night at Columbia Side 2; audiocassette TDK D-C 90, 1977 (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0255)
    - -Lung and Casandra Starke Interview // Lung, Cassandra, Parental Abuse Interview; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0256)
    - -The Manhattan Transfer Body and Souls / Wojnarowicz Public Radio; audiocassette TDK D 90, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0257)
    - -Paris-New York communications; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D - C60, undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0258)
    - -Phil Z/David W. (Connie) / Phil/David (1st tape); audiocassette (F-4B), undated (Box 16, Folder ID: 092.0259)
    - -Ben Neill/Dis-Solution 2 // Journal / White House Press Schedule; audiocassette TDK D 90, 1986 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0260)
    - -Ming Ma Cantonese / Performance tape (Languages) // Performance tape / Languages; audiocassette (F-4-D) Sony HF 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0261)
    - -Phil/David [2nd tape]; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK SA 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0262)
    - -D.W.NJ.G.T. June 89 / (1) If I Had $ (2) Cuz I (3) Last Nite I Took A Man Home (4) Vision Piece (5) Goddess of Life + Death // Kostabi / Phil died; audiocassette Panasonic C 60, 1989 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0263)
    - -Zwickler Demo A. Space; microcassette (F-4-A) Realistic MC-60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0264)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 1; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0265)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 2; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0266)
    - -Project Inform, Pt. 3; audiocassette Sony HF 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0267)
    - -Reading - Club 57; audiocassette (F-4-D) Scotch Dynarange 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0268)
    - -Releasing Guilt; audiocassette (F-4-G) TDK D-C 90, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0269)
    - -Richard Kern on Montanna 1990 (tape 1) // Richard Kern April 9 1990 RE: Montanna; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0270)
    - -Richard tape VII; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0271)
    - -(May 16 1982) NYC Self Conversations, Peters Loft, (RE: Sex / J.P. / Confusions); audiocassette TDK D-C 60 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0272)
    - -Short Essay on Photographs for Madoka, NYC 84 3-5 minutes; audiocassette TDK D 60, 1984 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0273)
    - -Sophie on Montanna, Tape V; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0274)
    - -Chosen to Stay + Fight; audiocassette (F-4-G) TDK D-C 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0275)
    - -Steve #; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0276)
    - -(Tape Journal) Clown laugh, use w/Doug // Recording #2 Steve Doughton, Philip Zimmerman, David W., Doug B. / Insane Laughter; audiocassette (F-4B) Maxell UD-XL II 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0277)
    - -Tape Journal; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0278)
    - -Tommy tape VI // Tommy -Montana [2] / Tommy (partial); audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0279)
    - -Tommy Turner on Montanna 1990 / 1/2 used: Tommy/Richard phone call; audiocassette (F-4B) TDK D 90 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0280)
    - -Tongues of Flame Opening, 7/26 - 27, 90 Normal, IL- NPR Interview / Opening + Interview Blinderman / Wojnarowicz, Ina Jaffee NPR; audiocassette (F-4-A) KCRW 89.9, 1990 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0281)
    - -Traveling; audiocassette (F-4B) Capitol music tape 60 minutes, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0282)
    - -Jan 1990 Panel Discussion w Paul Marcus, WBAI; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK SA 90 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0283)
    - -WBAI Panel w Paul Marcus; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK SA 90, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0284)
    - -WBAI Panel; audiocassette (F-4-A) TDK D 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0285)
    - -ITSOFOMO Copy; audiocassette 3M R120 DAT, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0286)
    - -Jan Bruce Audio Poetry; audiocassette Maxell UR 90, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0287)
    - -ITSOFOMO rough mix; audiocassette TDK SA 60, undated (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0288)
    - -ITSOFOMO Final Mix / Meat Bloody Memory War; audiocassette Maxell XL-II 100, 1991 (Box 17, Folder ID: 092.0289)
  - Subseries C: Sound Materials
    - -Broken piano/musak/jack hammer/Rev. Swaggart Mix; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0290)
    - -Bum Crash, Ship Horn, [Speed], Clocks, Firing Range, Chose to Stay & Fight; audiocassette (F-4-C) Ampex 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0291)
    - -Car crash; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 1, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0292)
    - -Fashion chit-chat, Queer dinner / Ready on the Right - Roll Back for El Salvadore Song; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0293)
    - -Gunfire Brian's song, Brian's song / Bum crash, Traffic report, Louis session 2; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 90, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0294)
    - -Hunger, Siren Pulse Beat, Buzzer, Surf / Crickets, Birds, Pool, Road Movie, Alcholism, Hold-up Tape [+] 10 Second; audiocassette TDK D-C 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0295)
    - -Windshield Wipers, [Buvsisles], Hut; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0296)
    - -KIDS; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 120, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0297)
    - -Mexico soundtrack; audiocassette (F-2) Maxell XLII 90, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0361)
    - -PRISON SEX, Sex Movie Music/Prison: Drums; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0298)
    - -Queer riot fragments; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 90, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0299)
    - -Reagan; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 1, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0300)
    - -Sounds: Reagan Shooting / Down & Out in Paris & London, [Asteroids] - Galaxian; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D-C 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0301)
    - -Reagan/various stations; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 3, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0302)
    - -Recorder/Harmonica; audiocassette Realistic Supertape HD-90., undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0303)
    - **Missing**-Recording session w/ Doug Bressler 4/18 (no year given); 1/4" audiotape (F-3), undated (Box 18, Folder no number)
    - -Garbage Truck in 14 St. Meat Market / Sex Movies; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0304)
    - -Soundtape II USA / Hostage, Sing a long Stuff, Jerry Falwell Stuff: How to Raise a Family for Fun etc., Flood News, etc. // Soundtape II USA; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0305)
    - -Soundtape USA #3 / Plane Taking off N. Mexico, Spanish Movie (Black Cat Appears), Bed Rock City (Dino Barking), Water, etc.; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0306)
    - -Sound Tape #4 Oregon / Rodeo Party Oregon, Rodeo Party Keith; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell LN 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0307)
    - -Soundtape #6; audiocassette (F-4-C) Realistic Supertape Gold 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0308)
    - -Soundtape #8, Alligator Tour, Louisianna, Storm Static Commercials; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0309)
    - -Sound Tape 1985 USA / Elvis's Home Memphis, Approx. 20 min., Frogs in Swamp outside Jackson Mississippi, Train? '', Steps, etc.; audiocassette Maxell XLI-S 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0310)
    - -Soundtape; audiocassette (F-4-C) Maxell XLII 90, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0311)
    - -Sound Tape, Oregon, Cows?, 6/2/95 C4 / Fire News/Prison Riot (Oregon) TV, Watermelon Pesticide, Fires, Rain Against Windows; audiocassette TDK D 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0312)
    - -South America Argentina - Car etc.; audiocassette Citacrom CHF 90, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0313)
    - - Storefront: -Dealers on Bowery Chrystie, Car Accident, 14 St., Union Square, Wash. Sq., etc., Chaco, Joe, Dealers on Rivington; audiocassette TDK D-C 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0314)
    - -Side A Only, 25 min. approx., Times Square, 42 st., Midnight, Sat. Nite, 10-15 Min., Bowery Traffic, 3rd St. // Wojnarowicz/Street; audiocassette Maxell XLII 90, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0315)
    - -Swaggart / Musak; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0316)
    - -Tracking plane / school kids; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK EC 6, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0317)
    - -Voices Distortion, Chosen to stay + fight; audiocassette (F-4-C) Ampex 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0318)
    - -Pt. Wind; audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0319)
    - -Wolf / George Jones, Amos Milburn; audiocassette (F-4-C) Sony CHF 90, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0320)
    - -Soundtape / NYC ambulance // Wojnarowicz: Soundtape; audiocassette (F-4-C) Sony HF 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0321)
    - -Crazy man sex house, audiocassette (F-4-C) TDK D 60, undated (Box 18, Folder ID: 092.0322)
  - Subseries D: Original Music/ Wojnarowicz & Others
    - -New Song - Eye ect. - Visitation, Wind Up Clock - Woman of the Moose - 3TK4-NM, 2/81 / Gacy Song; audiocassette Maxell LN C 60, 1981 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0323)
    - -3TK4; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK SA 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0324)
    - -3TK4 BLAK // 3TK4, Specials Reserve, Dishes, Fisherman, Too much too soon, Falling Out, Place to Hide / Bite like a kitty, Look Around, Machine Age, Divine Liar, La Diosa, Jackie Oh; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK D 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0325)
    - -3 Teens Kill 4; audiocassette (F-4-D) TDK D 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0326)
    - -Blank - Siren Cycle, Atomic Zone - Gun Cycle, 3 Teens - Atomic Zo; audiocassette (F-4-D) TDK D-C 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0327)
    - -Ben Neill, Two Dances / Mainspring c. 1986; audiocassette Maxell UDS-II 46 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0328)
    - -Ben Neill, Mainspring, c. 1988, The Living Room, Inc., New York, NY; audiocassette (type unknown) (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0329)
    - -Evan Lurie, Happy? Here? With You? In Spain?, solo piano 2/85 Seltzer; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK D 90, 1985 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0330)
    - -Evan Lurie, Pieces for Bandoneon; audiocassette (F-4-E) Maxell XLII-S 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0331)
    - -John Fekner, Dennis Lattman and Sasha Sumner c. 1986: 1) Final Concerto, 2) Oil Drum Mix; audiocassette Sony CHF 60 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0332)
    - -Rough mix, Visitation, Tell Me Something Good; audiocassette (F-4-E) TDK D-C 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0333)
  - Subseries E: Phone Message Tapes (in chronological order)
    - -1985- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 60 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0334)
    - -1985- phone message/ telephone '85; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 60 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0335)
    - -1987- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0336)
    - -1989- phone messages; microcassette (F-4-F) Code-A-Phone MC 60 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0337)
    - -4/31/90-5/1/90-"American Family bullshit etc."; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, 1990 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0338)
    - -6/2/92- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Certron LN 60, 1992 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0339)
    - -July 1992- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Panasonic C 60 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0340)
    - -May/ June (no year)- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0341)
    - -no date- "Time period of Pete's death" - Phone machine, phone message; audiocassette (F-1) TDK D 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0342)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Certron LN 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0343)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 30, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0344)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0345)
    - -no date- phone message side A; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0346)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0347)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony C 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0348)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) Sony CHF 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0349)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0350)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0351)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK SA 90, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0352)
    - -no date- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0353)
    - -no date- NEA messages; phone message, microcassette (F-4-F) Realistic MC-60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0354)
    - -no date- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Realistic MC-60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0355)
    - -no date- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0356)
    - -no date- phone message; microcassette (F-4-F) Sony MC 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0357)
    - -Unidentified Tape: audiocassette Sony EF 60, undated (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0358)
    - -Unidentified Tape: audiocassette, Maxell C 60 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0359)
    - -Unidentified Tape: audiocassette, Maxell UD XLI 60 (Box 19, Folder ID: 092.0360)
    - -no date- phone message; audiocassette (F-4-F) TDK D 90, undated
  - Subseries G: Dubbed Audiotapes
    - Subseries F: Dubbed Audiotapes, undated (Box 27, Folder no number)
    - Subseries F: Dubbed Audiotapes, undated (Box 28, Folder no number)
  - Subseries H: Unidentified/blank tapes
    - Subseries G: Unidentified/blank tapes, undated (Box 29, Folder no number)
- Series IX: Photography
  - Subseries A[1]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered envelopes 1 - 8
    - Envelope 1: Caven Point, NJ, 1984 w/Steve Brown, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Envelope 2: 1990, Illinois, Biology lab (great), Specimens in bottles, Louisiana, Great Airplane Clouds, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Envelope 3: Sexy guy from outside Springfield, MA, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Envelope 4: Louisiana 1988, toad, alligators (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Envelope 5: 1989, cross-country (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Envelope 6: Argentina (rewashed negs) truck @ night, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Envelope 7: James, Margarite, Luis et al., undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Envelope 8: Argentina trip, Luis painting his dad, ruins, dead dog, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Subseries A[2]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered envelopes 9 - 16
    - Envelope 9: Paris, 1982?, kid w/gun., undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Envelope 10: USA & South trip, Richard et al., undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Envelope 11: Paris, Germany, Berlin, 1983 -1984, Dean & Alan, alligator for mummy diptych, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Envelope 12: Warehouse, Jesse, doghead, 1983 - 1984 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Envelope 13: Rimbaud w/gun, self-portrait 1982 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Envelope 14: Pier graffiti, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Envelope 15: Mexico Super 8, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Envelope 16: Peter Hujar at pier (early 80s), Don Rodan with plane, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Subseries A[3]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered envelopes 17 - 21
    - Envelope 17: Tom/Virgin Islands (first trip w/Tom) late '85 or early '86, 1985 -1986 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Envelope 18: Luis & "family" with skeleton girl; Kern's house shooting up, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - NO Envelope 19, undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Envelope 20: Spain & Paris 1988; Dust series, sister Pat & baby (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Envelope 21: First photos (awful) & other early pics (some okay), some early warehouse photos; early self-portrait at 17, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Subseries A[4]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered envelopes 22 - 33
    - Envelope 22: Armed beetles, Dog wearing coat, Museum of Natural History, White House, Artwork, undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Envelope 23: L., undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Envelope 24: Koln, Paris, Great African sculpture, undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Envelope 25: Hujar: Newark tenement, dogs, iron yard, Tom Cochran: Caven Point, undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Envelope 26: Pep lounge, dance photos, undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Envelope 27: Mexico w/Tommy, undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Envelope 28: Mexico film stills, undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Envelope 29: Berlin (color), my graffiti on Berlin Wall, undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Envelope 30: Caven Point, NJ (before demolition), Peter Hujar, undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Envelope 31: Derby car crash (good ones), Kiki's leg, frog/neath water, undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Envelope 32: Brian Butterick, Jesse (10/22/80), 1980 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Envelope 33: Hujar in drag, undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Subseries A[5]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered enveloped 34 - 45
    - Envelope 34: Peter Hujar (first Hujar pics), "3 Teens" take, pier warehouse w/John, Hujar on farm, Cathy Underhill, undated (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Envelope 35: Nocht Nichts, undated (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Envelope 36: David's mother & Jean-Pierre, undated (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Envelope 37: IOLO, John Hall, Brian, undated (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Envelope 38: John Hall, early shots, Brian B, undated (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Envelope 39: 42 st., undated (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Envelope 40: Water damage, 189 Second Ave, Tom, train ride, undated (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Envelope 41: Factory fields, City Hall demo, peep show porn, undated (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Envelope 42: Color cockfight, photo prints by R., undated (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Envelope 43: Color Argentina, green truck (beautiful), store dummy, Iguazu falls, undated (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Envelope 44: Paris/Africa shop, spotted dog in forest, Gary Indiana, undated (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Envelope 45: Gun, Jesus, Time & Money, undated (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Subseries A[6]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered envelopes 46 -58
    - Envelope 46: Marion S., undated (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Envelope 47: Paul vacation, caterpillar, Jesse Helms photo, NYC, "on the prowl," Baltimore, Jersey train, undated (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Envelope 48: 1990 Illinois color, birds, unhatched specimens, undated (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Envelope 49: NYAC, Jesse etc, undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Envelope 50: Jesse/dream, undated (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Envelope 51: ACT UP Washington FDA (so-so), Washington Museum of Nat., undated (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Envelope 52: Paris, Brian, me, dead rat, undated (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Envelope 53: Shots of food posters, undated (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Envelope 54: Hujar loft, memorial alter piece w/candles, Beluga whales, undated (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Envelope 55: Peter/Jersey City, Beluga whale, undated (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Envelope 56: Steve Doughton playing dead in leaves, undated (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Envelope 57: Wash D., undated (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Envelope 58: Wash., undated (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Subseries A[7]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered "Box 108"
    - Death in the Cornfield series, Natural History Museum, Wash., undated (Box 36, Folder no number)
  - Subseries A[8]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered "Box 109," "Folder 110," "Paperbag 111"
    - Civilian Warfare poster, series of David w/heads, trip to Mexico, Rimbaud, undated (Box 37, Folder no number)
  - Subseries A[9]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered "Box 112-A"
    - Time/Money, Gun, crucifix, undated (Box 38, Folder no number)
  - Subseries A[10]: Contact Sheets
    Aperture-numbered "Box 112-B"
    - Language, cop, undated (Box 39, Folder no number)
  - Subseries A[11]: Contact Sheets
    Numbered envelopes 2 - 13
    - NO Envelope 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Envelope 2: Photos 1989, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Envelope 3: Kiki's Niece, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Envelope 4: Paris 1985, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - NO Envelope 5, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Envelope 6: Gay march/bigots/ACT UP, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Envelope 7: Newspaper article blowups, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Envelope 8: 1990 Paris, dust track series, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Envelope 9: News clips/tv images, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Envelope 10: Andreas skull rings, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Envelope 11: John Hall & I nude, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Envelope 12: New Mexico, Arizona, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Envelope 13: Paris, Africa shop, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Subseries A[12]: Contact Sheets
    Numbered envelopes 14 - 27
    - Envelope 14: Paris/NY, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Envelope 15: Paris/Lou's, undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Envelope 16: John wrapped head/Rimbaud, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Envelope 17: Michael A, undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Envelope 18: Susan Pyzow, undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Envelope 19: TV war, undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Envelope 20: Pittsburgh/Kiki, undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Envelope 21: Boston trips, undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - NO Envelope 22, undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Envelope 23: Self portrait/bird, undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Envelope 24: Caven Point, undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - NO Envelope 25, undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Envelope 26: Dirk w/gun, undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Envelope 27: Negatives, undated (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Subseries A[13]: Contact Sheets
    Numbered envelopes 28 - 41